Once upon a time, there was a maiden with wings of freedom.
A man in love with this maiden thought,
if I could just bind those wings,
we would never have to be apart even for a moment.
But when the man wrapped the maiden's wings in a magical shawl,
the wings immediately fell to the ground and the maiden died.
The man did not know that the maiden's wings were the source of her life.
At last, all the characters needed for the story have been assembled.
A prince without the heart to love, a knight who fears death, a villain without resolve,
and a princess who cannot express her love.
Something's still missing, though.
All right, you, go on.
And this time, don't you become interested in people's emotions.
Excuse me, won't you please take this?
It's quite lovely.
The name of this gem is...
Love.
I would advise you not to let it go.
It suits you.
No, I had no right to be holding on to such a thing.
Someone like me never did.
I see.
Thank you.
Princess Tutu is her.
I don't have any wish to fight you.
It doesn't matter who Princess Tutu is.
I will protect Muto in my own way.
I will be the one guarding him from the clutches of that raven.
Without fear.
I wonder if he really knows now.
You've been sighing all morning.
Poor thing.
The scar of rejection must truly run deep.
You seem happy.
Oh, me?
Thanks for worrying about me.
But it's not about being rejected or anything.
It's okay, Doc.
You don't have to tell us.
We know.
I don't have to tell you.
Anyway, revenge, revenge.
Come on, you've got to do it.
That's right.
You'll do it, won't you?
At any rate, you'll have to get him to notice you.
Yeah.
And that means a present.
Oh, that's good.
Then you'll see how he feels about you.
Really?
Fuck here, too.
Fuck here?
So, giving someone a present will reveal their feelings about you?
Oh, no.
You were listening?
He heard us.
Get a present now and he'll see you.
I'll tell your motive.
When you say present, what kind of thing do you mean?
He's probing us.
What do we do?
How do you think we should answer?
Say, Duck, what if it were you?
Duck would take anything, really.
That's right.
She'd take anything, anything she could get.
As long as it's given with love.
Gems or bars of solid gold.
Love?
There needs to be love?
Mr. Muto, I held a special class yesterday on being in love.
Perhaps I need to hold a special class on love itself.
Are you saying that there's a difference?
Of course there is.
If you do not grasp that, you will not be able to get married.
Would you care to sit in as well, Mr. Fakir?
No, thank you.
Then, Mr. Muto, let us go.
Gifts are perfectly fine, but such things as anti-flea collars can be rude, so discretion is necessary.
Does he know after all?
Fakir!
I want to ask you something.
Follow me.
What'd you want to ask me?
Princess Tutu.
Oh, come on!
You are, aren't you?
I'm surprised, to be honest.
Of all the people, I never expected it was you.
I want to ask you something, too.
Just like me, you're fighting to protect Muto, aren't you?
Then why do you keep trying to shatter his heart all the time?
Why?
That is something that has no bearing on the present situation, understand?
The tale can no longer be halted.
The tale?
If you wish to restore his heart, then go ahead.
No matter what the outcome of your little heroics, I will protect Muto.
Then why don't we work together?
And that way...
No, thank you.
But why not?
To put it simply, I don't trust you.
Muto, if you regain any more of your heart, you'll grow distant from me.
I know it.
I am a crow, your enemy.
Even though I love you so much.
I wish I could have stayed Rue forever, free of Krayi's memories.
But now...
Would anyone like some gems?
Would anyone like a gem to give your loved one as a gift?
Welcome.
Aren't you...
It's been a while, Rue.
As a gift?
Has this one bought your fancy?
The name of this gem here is love.
It's love?
I think it's beautiful.
Since you seem to like it so much, I shall give it to you.
Are you sure?
I am.
Please take this as I have no use for it.
Why don't you accept it, Muto?
And yet, though this gem is strong, it is easily scarred.
Though beautiful, it is easily tarnished.
If fought over, it may prove deadly.
Please use care in handling it.
You really like it that much?
So, you're going to give it to me, aren't you?
Rue.
Sorry.
This is...
I was just kidding.
I see.
I wonder who the lucky girl is.
That's not...
Could I see it for a second?
Sure.
It's beautiful, but it seems there's something important missing.
I wonder what...
What?
Really?
Shh!
I'm sorry.
I know it's precious to you.
Say, would you let me borrow it for tonight?
I'll fix it up and make it even prettier,
so that you can secure the heart of the one you love.
Okay.
The results ought to please you.
Mewtwo, I will not let anyone else have you.
I'll never hand you over.
Very good, very good.
Another necessary component of the tale has been added.
Love filled with hatred.
This is an interesting device, yes?
Fakir found out.
But it's kind of strange.
I actually feel relieved now.
To put it simply, I don't trust you.
Fakir's always thinking by himself.
Deciding by himself.
Fighting by himself.
Even...
Even crying by himself.
He won't show me his true face.
It was warm there, in Fakir's arms.
I bet that's the real Fakir.
Fakir.
Yes, what?
I'm thinking of giving a gift to Tutu.
That's so.
You're not angry?
Do as you wish.
Don't turn your sword against Tutu again.
Please, Fakir.
I want you to promise me...
I can't make that promise.
Now, please do not stoop!
Yes, sir!
Thanks for waiting.
What do you think?
It's wonderful.
Isn't it, though?
If you give this to the one you love,
you'll be able to secure her heart now.
And for all time.
Thank you, Rue.
I wish I could go home once
without having to stay after.
But, Mewtwo!
Mewtwo!
What was that?
I don't know what happened,
but I better go after him.
Protecting the prince is also
Princess Tutu's...
Thunder?
Mewtwo didn't have an umbrella, did he?
Where did he go?
Princess Tutu.
I wonder where she is.
I wonder where he went.
Would anyone like some gems?
Miss Edo!
Hi, Miss Edo!
It's been a while, hasn't it?
Now that you mention it,
it has been a while.
Anyway, Miss Edo,
have you seen Mewtwo around?
If you want Mewtwo,
he's searching for the one
to give his gift to.
Huh?
Mewtwo's gift?
So giving someone a present
will reveal their feelings about you?
What do you think of me?
I want to know.
I...
The one to give his gift to?
Oh, I know.
It's Roo, right?
With his feelings coming back,
he probably wants to know
how Roo feels and stuff.
Mm-hmm.
That's it.
But...
If the gift was for Tutu...
Well, even if that were true,
it's not for me as Duck,
but for Tutu,
so it really has nothing to do with me.
Nothing to do with me.
Thank you, Miss Edo!
Hmm.
Maybe he'll be looking somewhere
that he met Tutu.
Mewtwo!
Mewtwo, where are you?
Tutu...
Can I not see you,
Princess Tutu?
Tutu...
Mewtwo!
Is that Duck?
Mewtwo...
Why have you come here?
Oh, it seemed like it might rain,
and I thought you might not have an umbrella,
so I...
Are you waiting for someone?
Yes.
For Princess Tutu.
Huh?
Tell me, Duck,
do you know about Tutu?
What?
Oh, no, I don't, but...
Oh.
Um...
Please use this, okay?
Oh, thank you.
I hope you see her.
Yes.
Bye.
The one Mewtwo wants to see isn't me,
it's Princess Tutu, but...
Oh, my, that's dangerous.
That thought is truly dangerous.
Are you sure about this, Princess Tutu?
Can't I see her?
No, I don't see her.
My prince?
Is my prince searching for somebody?
Tutu.
My prince.
Finally.
I got a chance to see you.
It's lovely.
I'd like for you to accept this.
If that is what my prince wishes.
I'll put it on you.
Alright.
Oh, thank you.
That's strange.
What is?
They said if you give someone a gift, you'll know how they feel.
But I still don't know how you feel.
I don't know what it is you think of me.
That...
Although...
Huh?
It made you happy.
So I think that's okay too.
My prince.
What?
This is...
A heart shard.
Come on out.
What feeling are you supposed to be?
I am the feeling of love.
Oh, the feeling of love.
You are?
You don't have to wander any longer.
The place for you to return to is here.
I'm so glad.
Inside that ornament it was dark and those terrifying crows.
Ah!
Ay!
Ahh.
Ahh!
Ah!
Ahh.
Oh!
Jess!
T-T-T-T-T-T-T-T-T-T-T-T-T-T-T-T-T-T-T…
The feeling of love, is it?
I was hoping to dispatch Tutu with the gem,
but look what turned up.
And now I know your identity.
Grahi, what are you doing?
What?
Bakir!
Back off, you raven.
Oh my, that's dangerous.
That action is truly dangerous.
You may be the Knight Reborn,
but you're still just a human.
Are you sure of the course you're taking?
Then again, the princess is only a mere dark, isn't she?
And the prince is really nothing but a story.
It's dangerous not knowing your place in the world.
Oh, yes, and who might I ask?
Are you Princess Grahi?
Are you really the villain?
Are you really the raven?
How truly dangerous.
Don't you know the danger you put yourself in,
not knowing your place?
Stay away from Mewtwo.
Begone, you ugly crow!
No!
Craigie!
Ah!
Vakir!
You see, what did I just say, hmm?
If you're the knight, you have to conquer any fears you have and defeat the villain.
If you're the villain, you have to eliminate the princess without any show of mercy.
If you're the princess, you have to save the prince by the power of your love.
If you're the prince, you have to use your wisdom and courage.
Oh, I knew something was missing.
Yes, I am Princess Krehi.
Whatever I want, I will take by force.
What are you intending to do?
Krehi!
How do you like it, Princess Tutu?
Being bound by the prince's feelings?
What?
Hurts, yes.
Well, that only shows how strongly he feels for you.
How shameful.
No, Krehi!
Stop!
You love the prince, right?
But why?
Why would you do something so horrible?
Oh, dear.
The enemy now knows your identity and you've lost the prince.
How delightful.
How terrible.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha!
How terrible!
Time when I'd lost this necklace, you held on to it for me, remember, Fakir?
Would you hold on to it again?
It can't be that dull.
Have you regressed to the doll you used to be?
Because I withdrew that piece of your heart.
But this same knight was torn in two by the claws of the raven,
without the knight even landing a single blow with his sword.
A useless wretch who could only talk of protection.
Please, stop this malevolence now!
All you children who love stories, come gather round!
Fakir.